dozmia.com 2016-02-07

# DOZMIA PRIVACY POLICY

DOZMIA PRIVACY POLICY
This privacy policy (the “Policy”) explains how and for what purposes Dozmia Inc., and its related companies (collectively,
“Dozmia”, “we”, “us”, or “our”) collects, uses, and shares information of users (“you” or “your”) of the URL “www.dozmia.com” and
on other websites or apps that we own where this policy is posted (individually, and collectively, the “Site”).
The Policy contains 12 sections. You can go directly to each section by clicking the link below:
1. INTRODUCTION.
2. INFORMATION WE RECEIVE.
3. INFORMATION YOU SHARE WITH THIRD PARTIES.
4. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION.
5. HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION.
6. HOW YOU CAN VIEW, CHANGE, OR REMOVE INFORMATION.
7. SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION.
8. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
9. CONTACT INFORMATION.
10. GOVERNING LAW AND JURISDICTION.
11. LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES.
12. EFFECTIVE DATE.
1.        INTRODUCTION.
1.1.      Dozmia values the privacy of our users and takes the privacy of your information very seriously. We want to earn your trust
by being transparent about how the Site works. Please read this Policy carefully. By using the Site, you are agreeing to be bound by
this Policy.
1.2.      The Site is designed to make it easy for you to share your information with other users of the Site. You decide how much
information you feel comfortable sharing on the Site and you control how it is distributed through your privacy settings. You should
review the default privacy settings and change them if necessary to reflect your preferences. You should also consider your settings
whenever you share information.
1.3.      NO INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN UNDER 13. If you are under the age of thirteen (13), please do not attempt to
register for the Site, or provide any personal information about yourself to us. Anyone who provides their personal information to us
through the Site or otherwise represents that they are 13 years of age or older. If we learn that we have collected personal information
from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information
from or about a child under age 13, please contact us at: contact@Dozmia.com.
1.4.      PARENTAL PARTICIPATION. We strongly recommend that minors 13 years of age or older ask their parents for permission
before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet and we encourage parents to teach their children about
safe Internet use practices.
2.        INFORMATION WE RECEIVE.
2.1.      We may collect and process the following information about you:
          2.1.1. INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE US. This includes information about you that you provide when (i)
registering to use the Site, and (ii) using the Site. We may ask you to provide us with the following personal information:
          (a)       Your title, first name, surname, stage name, user name, gender, and date of birth;
          (b)       Your email address, postal address, and telephone number; and/or
          (c)       Your company, position, daytime telephone number, address, town/city, postcode and country. You may also
provide us with personal information if you contact us with a query.

           2.1.2.    We may also collect information regarding your usage of the Site, such as:
           (a)       SITE ACTIVITY INFORMATION. We may keep track of the actions you take on the Site, such as, details of your
visits to the Site, the resources you access, any data viewed, uploaded or downloaded, the number of times you view a particular
section of the Site, the music you listen to, and/or any comments you provide as a customer or user of the Site.
           (b)       ACCESS DEVICE AND BROWSER INFORMATION. When visiting the Site, we may log your computer
operating system type, browser type, browser language, the website you visited before browsing to the Site, pages you viewed, how
long you spent on a page, access times, Internet protocol (IP) address, information about your use of and actions on the Site, and
location data.
           (c)       COOKIE INFORMATION. We may log information using “cookies.” Cookies are small data files stored on your
hard drive by a website. We use cookies help us make our Site and your visit better.
           (d)       WEB BEACONS. We may log information using digital images called “web beacons” on the Site or in our emails.
We may use web beacons to manage cookies, count visits, and to learn what marketing works and what does not. We may also use
web beacons to tell if you open or act on our emails.
2.2.       If you do not provide information which we reasonably request, then you may not be able to access the full range of features
on the Site.
3.         INFORMATION YOU SHARE WITH THIRD PARTIES.
3.1.       We take steps to ensure that others use information that you share on the Site in a manner consistent with your privacy
settings, but we cannot guarantee that they will follow our rules. Please review this section to learn more about how you can protect
yourself when you share information with third parties.
3.2.       SHARING INFORMATION ON THE SITE. We designed our privacy settings to enable you to control how you share your
information on the Site. You should review the default privacy settings to make sure they reflect your preferences. You can control
the visibility of most of the information you share on the Site through the privacy settings you select. For example, through your
privacy settings, you can change the default setting that your music listening information is public to all visitors of the Site, so that
your music listening information is private.
3.3.       If you use an external source to publish information to the Site, you should check the privacy setting for that external source.
4.         HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION.
4.1.       We use your information to operate, maintain, and improve the Site. Specifically, we may use your information to do the
following:
           (a) Administer your accounts with us;
           (b) Process materials submitted by you;
           (c) Contact you with information about goods and services;
           (d) Provide you with information, products or services that you request from us;
           (d) Verify your identity;
           (e) Carry out marketing analysis and make general improvements to the Site;
           (f) Obtain your views or comments on the services we provide, or to ask you to participate in surveys;
           (g) Contact the winners of any competitions and help us plan other promotional activities;
           (h) Ensure that content from the Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;
           (i) Carry out our obligations arising from any contracts or agreements entered into between you and us; or
           (j) Protect, investigate, and deter against fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activity.
4.2.       We may also provide the public and/or third parties (e.g. advertisers, our licensors of musical compositions and/or sound
recordings, record labels, music publishers, musicians, songwriters, recording artists, personal managers, music agents, and music
attorneys) with aggregate information about our users. We may provide such aggregate information so that anyone can see the Site’s
data on music consumption and/or to help such third parties reach the kind of audience they want to target. However, we do not
disclose information about identifiable individuals to the public or to such parties.

4.3      We may also display your music listening information (e.g. the music you listen to and your name) to all visitors of the Site.
You can change your music listening information, including making it private, as described sections 3.2 and 6.1.
5.       HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION.
5.1.     We share your information with third parties when we believe the sharing is permitted by you, reasonably necessary to offer
our services, or when we are legally required to do so. Specifically, we may share your information as follows:
         (a) With your consent;
         (b) When we do a business deal, or negotiate a business deal, involving the sale or transfer of all or a part of our business or
assets;
         (c) For legal, protection, and safety purposes. For example, to comply with laws or to respond to lawful requests and legal
processes.
         (d) To protect our rights and property, and the rights and property of our agents, customers, and others. This includes
enforcing our agreements, policies, and terms of use.
         (e) In an emergency. This includes protecting the safety of our employees and agents, our customers, or any person;
         (f) With those who need it to do work for us; or
         (g) We may also share aggregated and/or anonymized data with others for their own uses.
6.       HOW YOU CAN VIEW, CHANGE, OR REMOVE INFORMATION.
6.1.     VIEWING AND EDITING YOUR PROFILE AND OTHER INFORMATION. You may change or delete your profile
information at any time by going to your profile page and clicking the appropriate link. You may also change whether your user
information (e.g. your music listening information) is public or private at any time by going to your privacy settings on the Site and
clicking the appropriate link. Information will be updated immediately.
6.2.     DEACTIVATING OR DELETING YOUR ACCOUNT. If you want to stop using your account you may deactivate or delete
it. When you delete an account, it is permanently deleted. When you deactivate an account, it is not permanently deleted. You should
only delete your account if you are certain you never want to use it. To deactivate or delete your account, you must contact us be
emailing your request to: contact@Dozmia.com.
6.3.     LIMITATIONS ON REMOVAL. Even after you remove information from your profile or delete your account, copies of that
information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been shared with others, it was otherwise distributed pursuant to your
privacy settings, or it was copied or stored by other users. Additionally, we may retain certain information to prevent identity theft and
other misconduct even if deletion has been requested.
6.4.     OPT OUT. If you do not want us to contact you in respect of goods or services, you may opt out at any time. You can
exercise this right at any time by either unsubscribing via the link in the email we send you, updating your settings, or by email:
contact@Dozmia.com. If you opt out, we may still send you non-marketing emails. Non-marketing emails include emails about your
accounts and our business dealings with you.
6.5.     You may send requests about personal information to: contact@Dozmia.com. You can request to change contact choices,
opt-out of our sharing with others, and update your personal information.
6.6.     You can typically remove and reject cookies from the Site with your browser settings. Many browsers are set to accept
cookies until you change your settings. If you remove or reject our cookies, it could affect how our Site works for you.
6.7      DO NOT TRACK. We do not currently respond to “Do Not Track” signals.
7.       SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION.
7.1.     We do our best to keep your information secure. However, no company can fully prevent security risks, mistakes may
happen, and bad actors may defeat even the best safeguards.
7.2.     Steps we take to keep your information secure. The Site uses a security system that protects any personal information that is
stored on our servers from unauthorized use. However, as no data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100%
secure, we cannot take responsibility for any unauthorized access or loss of personal information that is beyond our reasonable
control.

7.3.      RISKS INHERENT IN SHARING INFORMATION. Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your
information, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other users with
whom you share your information. We cannot guarantee that only authorized persons will view your information. We cannot ensure
that information you share on the Site will not become publicly available. We are not responsible for third party circumvention of any
privacy settings or security measures on the Site. You can reduce these risks by using common sense security practices such as
choosing a strong password, using different passwords for different services, and using up to date antivirus software.
7.4.      REPORT VIOLATIONS. You should report any security violations to us by emailing: contact@Dozmia.com.
7.5.      ENFORCEMENT. We regularly review our compliance with the Policy. If we receive a formal written complaint, we will
contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities to resolve any
complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.
8.        CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
8.1.      We may change this Policy at any time. If we make any changes, we will change the Effective Date below, and where
appropriate, may notify you via e-mail or announcement on the Site.
8.2.      By using the Site, you signify your acceptance of the revised privacy policy.
8.3.      We encourage you to periodically review the Site’s current privacy policy.
9.        CONTACT INFORMATION.
9.1.      If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Policy, please email us at: contact@Dozmia.com.
10.       GOVERNING LAW AND JURISDICTION.
10.1.     The Site is operated from the United States of America. By using the Site, you consent to having your personal information
transferred to and processed in the United States.
10.2.     Any dispute or claim arising out of or in connection with this Policy or its subject matter shall be governed by and construed
according the laws of the United States, without giving effect to any conflict of laws provisions.
11.       LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES.
11.1.     The Site may contain links to and from the websites of our partners, advertisers, and associates. If you follow a link to any of
these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability
for the protection of any data supplied to other sites.
12.       EFFECTIVE DATE.
12.1.     This Policy was last updated on September 3, 2014.
